https://www.episcopalretirement.com/corporate/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Articles and information contained within Episcopal Retirement Services’ website are intended for informational purposes only and should not be substituted for medical advice. Consult with your physician if you have questions about or concerns related to your personal health.
Our Commitment To Privacy:
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage.
The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on Episcopal Retirement Services’ website.
On some pages, you can submit an application for employment, make requests and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
Work history
On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you supply a name as a reference on an employment application, you will need to submit the reference’s phone number. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:
Name
Address
Phone number
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself only to complete your request. We do not share this information with outside parties.
We use the information you provide about someone else only to request a reference for employment. We do not share this information with outside parties.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose unless specifically requested, and are not shared with outside parties.
You can register with our website if you would like to receive occasional emails updating our products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security:
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy:
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by sending a request to the webmaster. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
How To Contact Us:
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at (513) 272-5555 ext. 4288 or send an email to breynolds@erslife.org.
Linkage Online - A Blog by ERS
ERS Linkage Podcast - Episode 25
Dec 3, 2020
At Home Exercises for Residents, Part 28: Around the Clock Steps
Nov 25, 2020
ERS Linkage Podcast - Episode 24
Nov 18, 2020
How to Choose a Retirement Community
Learn How to Find the Right Place to Live Well Into the Future
Sign up for our Newsletter
BLOG
Premier Communities
Deupree House
Marjorie P. Lee
Episcopal Church Home
Affordable Living
Cincinnati Area
Employee Resources
Since 1951, Episcopal Retirement Services has worked to improve the lives of older adults through innovative, quality senior living communities, and through community services for older adults.
3870 Virginia Ave.
Cincinnati, OH 45227
P: (513) 271-9610
E: info@erslife.org
Copyright ©2020 ERS. All Rights Reserved.
Privacy | Protected Health Information Disclosure | Residential Rights
